expo.io 2018-12-28

# Expo — Privacy policy

## General Information

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Expo is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Expo will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

#### Information Gathering and Usage

When you register for Expo we ask for information such as your name and e-mail address. Expo uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

#### Cookies

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.
  * Cookies are required to use the Expo service.
  * We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to re-login to your Expo account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

#### Data Storage

Expo uses third-party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Expo. Although Expo owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Expo projects, you retain all rights to your data.

#### Usage Statistics

We collect usage and performance statistics from Expo projects. Usage statistics are transmitted using TLS and help us improve future versions of Expo.

#### Disclosure

Expo may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

#### EU and Swiss Safe Harbor

If you choose to provide Expo with your information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States.

#### Changes

Expo may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your Expo account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

#### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [support@expo.io](mailto:support@expo.io)
